A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers, Inc. (RBI) (and successors) records FA480
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Investments, A-Z, Accession 1, 1946-1969; 1936-1984; 1; 97.21 Cubic Feet 251 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes; Standard storage boxes, Boxes 1-94.
  - Eastern Airlines - Management Bulletins, 1957-1959 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Airlines - Mergers - General, 1959-1963 (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
    Eastern-American, 1961-1963. Northeast-National-Mohawk, 1961. United, 1959.
  - Eastern Airlines - Report on Pensions, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Airlines - Merger - Clippings, 1938-1963 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Eastern Airlines - Study - Celig Altschul, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Airlines - Reports, 1940-1959 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - ITEK Corporation - Agreement, 1959-1965 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Eastern Airlines - Proposed Eastern-American Merger (Box 41, Folder 3-5, Box 42, Folder 1-4)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors, 1964-1966 (Box 43, Folder 1-3, Box 44, Box 45, Folder 1-4)
    LSR Investment. RBM, HW, TFW, FHD, WJM, RHS, POC. Includes Finance Committee and other committees.
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 1-3, Box 47, Folder 1-4, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors, 1967-1968 (Box 51, Folder 1-4, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Folder 1-2)
  - Ecuador Sulphur Co., 1966 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    No investment. WR.
  - Education - Teaching Machines, 1961-1962 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    LSR interest, No investment. POC, HW.
  - Education - Programmed Instruction, 1961-1962 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Educational Sciences, Inc., 1962 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    Systems and curriculum consultants to educational institutions. LSR interest, no investment. HW, POC, CES.
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    No investment. HW.
  - Electronic Reduction Corp., 1947-1956 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    Production of beryllium chloride for commercial use. DR investment. PFK, RBM.
  - Electronic Specialty Co. - General, 1958-1968 (Box 55, Folder 1-3)
    Investment and management.
  - Electronic Specialty Co. - Directors (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Specialty Co. - Financing (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Electronic Specialty Co. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - General, 1959-1967 (Box 56, Folder 4-5, Box 57, Folder 1)
    LSR investment. CHB, RBM, HW, TFW.
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Agreements, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Annual Reports, 1960-1963 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Competitors, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Directors Meetings, 1961-1965 (Box 57, Folder 5, Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Bank Loans, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Dudley Purchase, 1960 December-1961 January (Box 58, Folder 3-4)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Voting Trust Agreement, 1961-1962 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Warrants, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Facilities, 1964-1965 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Financing, 1960-1965 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Dukane Corporation, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - International Division, 1961-1965 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Merger - General, 1960-1964 (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Mergers, 1960-1964 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Bank Engineering, Co., Corrigan Communications, Inc., SCM Corporation, Science Research Associates, and Tele-Cine, Inc.
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Newhall Report, 1963-1964 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Projections, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Proposal to FAA, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Teaching Aids, 1961-1964 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Zues Soucek Consultant, 1964-1965 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Stockholders Meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Stock Options and Stockholders Lists, 1964-1966 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Teaching Research and Technology, 1961-1964 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Teaching Research and Technology - Troutman, John E., 1964 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Work Sheets (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Summary (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Brochures (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Teaching Labs - Product Literature (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Electronics Corporation of Israel, 1962-1965 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    ARM, LSR, DR investments. RHS, JRD.
  - Energy Conversion, 1961-1964 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    No investment. POC.
  - Epstein and Carrol Associates, 1959-1964 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Publishing company. LSR investment.
  - Erickson, Rodney, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Universal Broadcasting Co. No investment. RBM, WTL.
  - FMA, Inc. - Summary, 1959-1966 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - FMA, Inc. - General, 1959-1967 (Box 63, Folder 4-5, Box 64, Folder 1)
    Information retrieval service. ARM, LSR investments. TFW, POC, HW, RBM, CHB.
  - FMA, Inc. - Audits, 1959-1967 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - FMA, Inc. - Brochures, 1959-1967 (Box 64, Folder 3, Box 65, Folder 1-3, Box 66, Folder 1)
  - FMA, Inc. - Directors Meetings, 1961-1967 (Box 66, Folder 2-4, Box 67, Folder 1-4, Box 68, Folder 1-3)
  - FMA, Inc. - Eastern Airlines Proposal (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - FMA, Inc. - Facilities, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - FMA, Inc. - File Search, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 1-4)
  - FMA, Inc. - Financing, 1960-1965 (Box 69, Folder 5, Box 70, Folder 1-2)
  - FMA, Inc. - Kilfitt, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - FMA, Inc. - Media, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - FMA, Inc. - Mergers (Box 70, Folder 5, Box 71, Folder 1)
  - FMA, Inc. - Newell, C.W. - Report, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - FMA, Inc. - Ricoh Company, Ltd., 1962-1964 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - FMA, Inc. - Tapes from Brussels, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - FMA, Inc. - Cutler-Hammer, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
  - FMA, Inc. - ETI, 1963-1967 (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
  - FMA, Inc. - Stock Holdings and Options, 1962-1967 (Box 72, Folder 3-4, Box 73, Folder 1-2)
  - Family Airplane - General, 1957-1963 (Box 73, Folder 3, Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Family Airplane - Beechcraft, 1956-1959 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Family Airplane - Gruman, 1958-1962 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Farley Associates, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Investment company. No investment. JRD
  - Fifth-Madison Corp., 1936-1954 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    JDR 3rd investment. RHM.
  - Filtisaf - General Correspondence, 1946-1962 (Box 74, Folder 6, Box 75, Folder 1)
    Congolese mining company. NAR and LSR investment. JRD, JJ, RHM.
  - Filtisaf - Financial, 1946-1955 (Box 75, Folder 2-3)
  - Filtisaf - Managing Committee, 1947-1960 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Filtisaf - Board of Directors, 1947-1953 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Fitzpatrick, Donald, 1960-1961 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    Brown-Durell company. No investment. COG.
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - General, 1952-1961 (Box 75, Folder 7, Box 76, Folder 1)
    LSR Investment. RBM, HW, TFW, WHM.
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Articles of Incorporation, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Directors Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Directors Meetings, 1958-1961 (Box 76, Folder 5-6, Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Annual Reports, 1954-1961 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Facilities, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Financial and Financing, 1953-1955 (Box 77, Folder 4-6)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Merger Discussions, 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 1-4)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Patents, 1951-1959 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Stock Interests, 1953-1960 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Stock Options, 1953-1960 (Box 79, Folder 3-4)
  - Flight Refueling, Inc. - Summary (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Flight Refueling, Ltd., 1952-1960 (Box 79, Folder 6-8)
    British Corporation which invested in Flight Refueling, Inc.
  - Flight Safety Foundation - General, 1948-1963 (Box 80, Folder 1-5, Box 81, Folder 1-2)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Aviation Underwriters Association, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - European Advisory Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Executive Committee Meetings, 1948-1963 (Box 82, Folder 2-3, Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Financial, 1948-1963 (Box 83, Folder 2, Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Fundraising, 1948-1961 (Box 84, Folder 2-3, Box 85, Folder 1-2)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Guggenheim Aviation Center, 1950-1961 (Box 85, Folder 3, Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Industry Advisory Committee Meetings, 1956-1958 (Box 86, Folder 2-3)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Organization, 1962-1964 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Reports and Publications, 1950-1963 (Box 86, Folder 5-8, Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Flight Safety Foundation - Letters of Comment, 1948-1960 (Box 87, Folder 2-4)
  - Floats, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    Design, construction and exhibition of floats. No investment. WJM, RBM, POC, TFW.
  - Florida Timber Project, 1955 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    No investment. RBM, GCW.
  - Flow Labs, 1961-1964 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    Biochemical fuel cells research. No investment. POC, HW.
  - Foundation Library Center, 1962-1963 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    Survey of investment funds. REF filled out questionnaires. JEL, JRD, WDD.
  - Four Star TV, 1961-1963 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    Producers of film series. No investment. POC.
  - Foreign Investments - Department, 1950-1962 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Reports filed by RBI on "Filatures et Tissages Africaines" in Belgian Congo with DOC.
  - Gaertner, W.W., 1962-1963 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Employee of CBS Labs. CBS.
  - Gaither, H. Rowan, 1954-1960 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Chromatic Television Labs employee. No investment.
  - Gambrell, E. Smythe, 1960-1963 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    Personal friend of LSR. HW.
  - Garsite Products, 1959 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    Vapor removal system. No investment. RBM.
  - General Applied Science Labs - General-Summary, 1958-1964 (Box 88, Folder 6-8)
    LSR Investment. HW, RBM, TFW.
  - General Applied Science Labs - NTDC Contract, 1962-1963 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - General Applied Science Labs - Contract Status, 1959-1964 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - General Applied Science Labs - Directors Meetings, 1959-1966 (Box 89, Folder 2-4)
  - General Applied Science Labs - Facilities - General, 1959-1964 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Fairchild Engine Corp.
  - General Applied Science Labs - Financing, 1958-1965 (Box 90, Folder 2-3, Box 91, Folder 1)
    5 Percent Loan, Original Financing, Small Business Application, Voting Trust Agreement, By-Laws.
  - General Applied Science Labs - Stockholders Meetings, 1959-1965 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - General Applied Science Labs - Intercontinental Instruments, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - General Applied Science Labs - Janus Products, 1962-1964 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - General Applied Science Labs - Lumatron Electronics, 1963-1964 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - General Applied Science Labs - Mergers - General, 1959-1964 (Box 91, Folder 6-7)
    Italian Organization, Aero-Chem Research Labs, North Hill Electronics.
  - General Applied Science Labs - Stock Options, 1959-1964 (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
  - General Applied Science Labs - Brochures (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - General Dynamics - Convair, 1957-1964 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - General Dynamics - General Atomic, 1962-1964 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - General Electric Credit Corp., 1948-1960 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    RBF investment.
  - General Technology Corp. - Financial, 1960-1964 (Box 93, Folder 4-5)
    LSR investment. RBM, TFW, WJM.
  - Geonautics, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    Applied geophysics. No investment. TFW, RBM.
  - Geophysics Corporation of America - General, 1958-1962 (Box 93, Folder 7, Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Geophysics Corporation of America - Directors Meetings, 1964-1968 (Box 94, Folder 2-3, Box 95, Folder 1-3, Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Geophysics Corporation of America - Mergers - General, 1959-1964 (Box 94, Folder 4-5, Box 95, Folder 4, Box 96, Folder 2)
    Dynaform, Co., Mt. Vernon Research Co., Vacuum Electronics Corp.
  - Geophysics Corporation of America - Reports and Studies, 1958-1965 (Box 292, Folder 3-4, Box 293, Folder 1-4, Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Geophysics Corporation of America - Directors Meetings, 1959-1965 (Box 294, Folder 2-3, Box 295, Folder 1-4)
  - Great American Insurance Company, 1965 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Great Southwest Corp. - General, 1960-1971 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Construction and promotion of recreation facilities. Industrial districts, warehouses, apartment buildings. LSR investment. JRD, HW, RBM.
  - Great Southwest Corp. - Agreements, 1958-1959 (Box 97, Folder 1-4, Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Great Southwest Corp. - Reports and Studies (Box 98, Folder 1-3, Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Great Southwest Corp. - SEC Documents, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Gila River Ranch, 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Cattle ranch. No investment. WTL, JRD.
  - Gould Paper Co., 1953-1955 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    No investment. IBEC interest. AWH, RBM.
  - Gray Industries, Inc., 1966 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    Medical technology. No investment. Processes and procedures offered to Sloan-Kettering.
  - Grand Central Rocket Company, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Greenrock Corp., 1961 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    Family investment. RO, RBM.
  - Griswold, Roger W. II, 1950-1960 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    Griswold Aeronautical Corp. No investment. HW, TFW.
  - Hallicrafters Co., 1960-1962 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    Electronics concern. LSR investment. HW, TFW.
  - Harmon, William H. Corp. - General, 1946-1950 (Box 100, Folder 7-9, Box 101, Folder 1-2)
    Building contractor. LSR investment. HW, AWH.
  - Harmon, William H. Corp. - Incorporation, 1947-1948 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Harmon, William H. Corp. - Chase Bank, 1948 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Harmon, William H. Corp. - Market Guarantee Agreement, 1947-1948 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Harmon, William H. Corp. - Prospectus, 1947-1948 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Harmon, William H. Corp. - Publicity, 1947-1948 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Harmon, William H. Corp. - Small Homes Development Corp., 1947-1952 (Box 102, Folder 2-3)
  - Harmon, William H. Corp. - Stock Interests, 1948 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Harmon, William H. Corp. - West Briar Corp., 1950-1951 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Hawker, Siddley, 1953-1963 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    Manufacturer of aircraft. No investment. TFW.
  - Heath de Rochment Corp. - D.C. Heath, 1963 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    Textbook publishing company. No investment. JRD, WDD.
  - Heller, Robert & Associates, 1963-1965 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    Management consultant firm. No investment. PB, HW.
  - Helmore Reaction Simulator, 1961-1964 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    No investment. CBS.
  - Highstown Rug Co., 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    No interest or investment. JRD, CBS
  - Hilburn, Earl D., 1958 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    Computer work. No investment. RBM, WJM.
  - Hiller Aircraft, 1947-1959 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    No investment. HW, TFW.
  - Hitchcock, Ethan Allen, 1956-1962 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    Korean steel mill. No investment. RBM.
  - Hi-Temp Wires, Inc., 1956 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    Merger between Hi-Temp and AIL considered. RBM.
  - Honolulu Oil Corp. - Production Payment Loan, 1961-1964 (Box 103, Folder 5-6, Box 104, Folder 1-3, Box 105, Folder 1-2)
    LSR investment. RBM, HW, TFW.
  - Honolulu Oil Corp. - Reports, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Hooker Chemical Co. - Merger with Occidental Petroleum (Box 105, Folder 4)
    LSR investment. RHS.
  - Hooker Chemical Co. - Udylite Merger (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Hooker Chemical Co. - Terra Chemicals International (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Hooker Chemical Co. - SEC (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Hooker Chemical Co. - Loan Agreement, 1964 May (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Hooker Chemical Co. - Directors Meetings, 1963-1967 (Box 106, Folder 4-7, Box 107, Folder 1-4, Box 108, Box 109)
  - Hoover, Allan, 1958 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    Consultant for Horizons, Inc. Service used. RBM.
  - Horizons, Inc. - Allan Hoover's files, 1954-1958 (Box 110, Folder 2-3)
  - Horizons, Inc. - General, 1949-1958 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    Mining company. LSR investment. RHS, RBM, HW.
  - Horizons, Inc. - Titanium Corporation, 1955-1963 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    Corporation Documents. Stockholders.
  - Horizons, Inc. - Titanium Corporation - Stock Interests, 1951-1955 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Horizons, Inc. - Titanium Corporation - Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Horizons, Inc. - Zirconium Corp., 1953-1955 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Hughes Laser Group, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    No investment. POC, TFW.
  - Hughes Tool Co., 1954 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    Owned by Howard Hughes. Discussions between LSR and HH. Interest shown, but no investment made. RHM, JEL.
  - Hunsaker, S.V. and Sons, 1962-1964 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    Subdividers and builders of homes. No investment. WDD.
  - Hunter Manufacturing Corp., 1955-1956 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    Briston Engineering Corp. Possible merger with FRI discussed. RBM.
  - Hycon Manufacturing Co., 1953-1965 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Manufacture aircraft. No investment. HW.
  - Hydrofoils - Hydrofoil Lines, 1963 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    LSR investment. HW, RBM, CBS.
  - Hydrofoils - American Hydrofoils, 1963-1964 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Hydrofoils - Grumman Aircraft Engineering, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Hydro-Space Technology, 1962 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    No investment. CHB, CBS.
  - Index and Retrieval Systems, 1962 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    No investment. POC, TFW, HW.
  - Indussa Corp., 1957-1960 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    Industrial sales company. IBEC transferred stock to LSR, who later sold interest. PFK.
  - Industrial Research, 1960-1963 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    Publication. No investment. CHB, TFW, HW.
  - Industrial Rockets, 1955-1957 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    No investment. TFW, HW.
  - Information for Industry, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    No investment. RBM, TFW.
  - Information Handling Services, Inc., 1961-1965 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    Possible merger with FMA discussed. TFW.
  - Information Retrieval, 1961-1963 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    Microfilm process. No investment. POC.
  - Institute for Defense Analysis, 1957-1963 (Box 113, Folder 1-4, Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Educational Technology, 1963 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    No investment. CBS, TFW.
  - Institute for Scientific Information, 1962-1967 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Inter-Company Seminar, 1959-1961 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    Office participation. HW, TFW.
  - International Aerospace Center, 1962-1964 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    Foreign trade center for aerospace industry. No investment. TFW, HW
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - General Correspondence, 1947-1960 (Box 114, Folder 6, Box 115, Folder 1)
    Family investments. JJ, RBM, HW, WJM.
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - Capitalization, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - International Cooperation Administration - Investment Guarantee Division, 1961 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    Investment guarantee division. No investment, some interest. RHS.
  - International Electronic Research Corp., 1961 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    No investment. POC, RJS, TFW.
  - International Nickel - LSR Stock Holdings, 1948-1961 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    LSR investment. RBM, HW, RHS.
  - International Nickel - Stock Options, 1955-1959 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - International Petroleum Co., Ltd., 1946-1956 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    LSR & NAR interest, but no investment. RHM.
  - International Products Corp., 1958-1959 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    Oil and gas exploration in Paraguay. No investment. JRD, GFM.
  - International Research Corp., 1956-1957 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    No investment. HW, TFW, RBM.
  - International Research Institute, 1959-1967 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    No investment. TFW.
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity, 1964-1965 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    Rodman C. Rockefeller is director. NW.
  - Intertech Corp., 1959-1964 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    Engineering research. No investment. CBS.
  - Interphase Corp., 1965 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Engineering research. No investment. CBS, RBM.
  - IRECO Chemicals, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    Produce chemical supplies. TFW. CBS. No investment.
  - Island Packers - General, 1947-1958 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    South Sea Fishery. LSR investment. JJ, AWH, RBM.
  - Island Packers - Navy Lease, 1948 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Island Packers - Reorganization, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 5-6)
  - Island Packers - Stock Interests, 1952 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Itek - General, 1957-1960 (Box 116, Folder 7, Box 117, Folder 1-2)
    Family interest. HW, RBM, WJM.
  - Itek - Audits, 1961-1962 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Itek - Financial - Budgetary Control, 1959 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Itek - Financial - Compensation Review Committee, 1963 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Itek - Financial - Loan Agreements, 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Itek - Management Survey - H.U. Hunt (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Itek - Mergers - General, 1961-1963 (Box 118, Folder 2-4, Box 119, Folder 1)
    Separated Materials
    Broadview Research. Dialaphone, Inc. Dictaphone. Ditto. Harris Intertype.
  - Itek - Mergers - Electro-Products, 1961-1962 (Box 119, Folder 2-3)
  - Itek - Mergers - Kilfitt, 1961-1963 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Itek - Mergers - Hermies Electronics, 1960-1961 (Box 120, Folder 2-3)
  - Itek - Mergers - Itek Labs, 1961-1962 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Itek - Mergers - Vectron, 1958 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Itek - Mergers - Photostat, 1959-1962 (Box 120, Folder 6, Box 121, Folder 2-4, Box 122, Folder 1-2)
  - South Seas Marine Products, Ltd. - Snapshots, Fiji Islands, 1962-1964 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Itek - Mergers - Vidya - Financial Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Itek - Mergers - Vidya - Directors Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 122, Folder 4, Box 123, Folder 1-2)
  - Itek - Mergers - Vidya - Meetings, 1959-1962 (Box 123, Folder 3, Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Itek - Mergers - Vidya - Agreements, 1959 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Itek - Mergers - Vidya - Stock Options, 1959-1962 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Itek - Mergers - Vidya - Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Itek - Organization Charts and By-laws, 1960-1961 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Itek - Progress Reports, 1960-1964 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Itek - New Product Program (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Itek - Prospectus (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Itek - Time, Inc. (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Itek - Space Recovery Systems (Box 125, Folder 5, Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Itek - Progress Reports, 1960-1968 (Box 126, Folder 2-4, Box 127, Folder 1-3, Box 128, Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Itek - Directors Meetings, 1959-1967 (Box 129, Folder 2-5, Box 130, Folder 1-4, Box 131, Box 132, Box 133, Box 134, Folder 1-3)
  - JIL Aircraft, Inc., 1965 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    LSR interest, No investment.
  - Johnson and Higgins, 1950-1962 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    Consultants for employee benefit plans. Made study of DR insurance plans. RBM, WJM, HW.
  - Jones and Gillies, 1946-1967 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    Aviation consultants. Service used. HW, TFW, RBM.
  - KRS Electronics, 1961-1962 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    No investment. CHB, HW.
  - Kellett Aircraft Corp., 1948-1961 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    No investment. CBS, HW.
  - Kentucky Finance Co., 1961-1963 (Box 135, Folder 3-4)
  - Kenyon Investment Co., 1952-1960 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Kolker Chemical Corp., 1960-1962 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    PB was director. PB, RBM. General, Sale of Stock, and Singmaster and Breyer.
  - Kroeger, A and H. Corporation, 1962-1965 (Box 135, Folder 7)